=Love For Two Lives=
= الحب لعمرين =
=Episode 4=
= الحلقة 4 =
Ready?
مستعد؟
Yes.
نعم.
(Oh, no.)
(أوه ، لا.)
(I'll see how you get away with that.)
(سأرى كيف تفلت من ذلك.)
(How dare you fight for the title with my family?)
(كيف تجرؤ على القتال من أجل اللقب مع عائلتي؟)
(Save me!)
(انقذني!)
Wait.
انتظر.
Step down.
انزل.
Queen Mother,
الملكة الأم ،
I have something to tell you.
لدي شيء لأخبرك به.
My Queen
ملكتي
is not Princess Xiangxiang.
ليست الأميرة Xiangxiang.
She's not?
هي ليست؟
So who is she?
إذن من هي؟
An imposter?
دجال؟
I asked her to do all of this.
طلبت منها أن تفعل كل هذا.
If Queen Mother has to blame someone,
إذا كان على الملكة الأم أن تلوم شخصًا ما ،
just blame me.
فقط ألومني.
(He's a loyal person though.)
(إنه شخص مخلص رغم ذلك).
I see.
أرى.
Queen.
ملكة.
Is the King telling the truth?
هل الملك يقول الحقيقة؟
Yes, Your Majesty.
نعم يا صاحب الجلالة.
I'm not Princess Xiangxiang.
أنا لست الأميرة شيانغشيانغ.
But,
ولكن،
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
We really love each other.
نحن حقا نحب بعضنا البعض.
The fruit of our love is inside me.
ثمر حبنا بداخلي.
I beg you, Your Majesty.
أتوسل إليك يا صاحب الجلالة.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
You are going to be a father soon.
ستصبح أبًا قريبًا.
Yes, Queen Mother.
نعم الملكة الأم.
We love each other.
نحب بعضنا البعض.
Please allow us to be together.
من فضلك اسمح لنا أن نكون معا.
If you have to punish one of us,
إذا كان عليك معاقبة أحدنا ،
just punish me.
فقط عاقبني.
Since you love each other,
بما أنكما تحب بعضكما البعض ،
and now she's pregnant,
وهي الآن حامل ،
what can I say?
ماذا استطيع قوله؟
I'll let it pass today.
سأتركها تمر اليوم.
Thank you, Queen Mother.
شكرا لك الملكة الأم.
But,
ولكن،
since you are not Princess Xiangxiang,
بما أنك لست الأميرة شيانغشيانغ ،
we'll have to reconsider
سيتعين علينا إعادة النظر
who is more suitable
من هو أكثر ملاءمة
to be the Queen.
لتكون الملكة.
I'm going to be an intern Queen?
سأكون ملكة متدربة؟
Shut up.
اسكت.
I'm totally beat.
أنا متغلب تمامًا.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Is my job finished?
هل انتهى عملي؟
Can you be the Queen for two more months?
هل يمكنك أن تكون الملكة لشهرين آخرين؟
What? Two more months?
ماذا؟  شهرين آخرين؟
No way.
مستحيل.
The Queen Mother would never let me be the Queen.
الملكة الأم لن تسمح لي أن أكون الملكة.
I've proposed to Princess Guzha in Qixi Kingdom.
لقد اقترحت على الأميرة Guzha في مملكة Qixi.
I need two more months.
أحتاج شهرين إضافيين.
During that time,
خلال ذلك الوقت،
you don't need to be the real Queen.
لست بحاجة إلى أن تكون الملكة الحقيقية.
You just need to
أنت فقط بحاجة إلى
pass her tests.
اجتياز اختباراتها.
No, no.
مهووس.
I'm not a trainee working to be the Queen.
أنا لست متدربة أعمل لأكون الملكة.
Your mom would never choose me.
والدتك لن تختارني أبدا.
She said she'd test me,
قالت إنها ستختبرني ،
but she'll only try to kill me.
لكنها ستحاول فقط قتلي.
You don't need to pay for the wall.
لا تحتاج لدفع ثمن الجدار.
I'll cover that myself, okay?
سأغطي ذلك بنفسي ، حسنًا؟
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
No, farewell.
لا وداعا.
(Bank customer service)
(خدمة عملاء البنك)
(On speaker)
(على مكبر الصوت)
(Hello.)
(مرحبًا.)
(Your bill this month is 4388 Yuan.)
(فاتورتك هذا الشهر هي 4388 يوان.)
I was just kidding.
كنت أمزح فقط.
Our fate led us
قادنا مصيرنا
where we are now.
اين نحن الان.
I can be your Queen.
يمكنني أن أكون ملكتك.
But maybe you can pay me...
لكن ربما يمكنك أن تدفع لي ...
Right?
حق؟
6000 Yuan per month,
6000 يوان في الشهر ،
with housing fund and insurances.
مع صندوق الإسكان والتأمينات.
And,
و،
you take half of my house,
تأخذ نصف منزلي ،
so you need to pay half of the rent.
لذلك عليك أن تدفع نصف الإيجار.
And water, electricity, internet cost.
والمياه والكهرباء وتكلفة الإنترنت.
Okay.
تمام.
Two months. No renewal.
شهرين.  لا تجديد.
♪Traces of time and space, and forgotten galaxies♪
آثار الزمان والمكان ، والمجرات المنسية
♪Time alternates our relationship♪
الوقت يتناوب علاقتنا ♪
♪The sea of stars is pretty and quiet♪
♪ بحر النجوم جميل وهادئ
♪The rain touches the breath♪
المطر يمس النفس ♪
♪Get close to you♪
♪ اقترب منك